Undergods is a fantasy, science fiction, drama film directed by Chino Moya.
An otherworldly journey through a Europe in decline - a collection of darkly
humorous, fantasy tales about ill-fated characters and doomed fortune.
K, played by Johann Myers.
Z, played by Géza Röhrig.
Ron, played by Michael Gould.
Ruth, played by Hayley Carmichael.
Harry, played by Ned Dennehy.
Reed The Estate Agent, played by Simon Manyonda.
Burn Hugh Gorman (born 1 September 1974) is an English actor.
He is known for his television roles as Owen Harper in the BBC series Torchwood (2006–2008), Karl Tanner in the HBO series Game of Thrones (2013–14), Major Edmund Hewlett in the AMC series
Turn: Washington's Spies (2014–2017), 'The Marshal' in the Prime Video series The Man in the High Castle (2015), and Adolphus Murtry in Prime Video series The Expanse (2019).
His film roles include Phillip Stryver in Christopher Nolan’s The Dark Knight Rises (2012), Hermann Gottlieb in Guillermo del Toro’s Pacific Rim (2013) and its sequel Pacific
Rim: Uprising (2018), Commander Hoff in The Hunger Games: The Ballad of Songbirds and Snakes, and Father Damien in Tim Burton's Beetlejuice Beetlejuice (2024).
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and emotional.